College of Engineering and Applied Sciences Records
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
College of Engineering and Applied Sciences Records2000-2015
nam_ua670
Administrative records of the College, formerly known as the College of Computing and Information, contains programs in Informatics, Computer Science, and Information Studies.
State University of New York at Albany. College of Engineering and Applied Sciences.
15 cubic ft.
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives, University at Albany, SUNY
Web Archives
Administrative History
The College of Computing and Information (CCI) was originally formed in 2005 from the School of Information Science and Policy and contained the Computer Science and Information Studies departments. In 2015, the school was renamed the College of Engineering and Applied Sciences and a new program in Computer Engineering was developed.
Collection contains administrative records, such as internal assessments, meeting minutes, correspondence, budgetary information, grant proposals, and documentation of events and major programatic changes.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection has no series, the original order of the material was kept.
Acquisition Information
All items in this collection were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives by Assistant Dean Nan Carroll. 2015 August
Access
Access to this collection is restricted. Portions of the collection may contain recent administrative records and/or personally identifiable information. Please contact an archivist for more information.
Red asterisks (***) denote restricted items.
Subject and Genre Headings
State University of New York at Albany.; State University of New York at Albany. College of Engineering and Applied Sciences.; State University of New York at Albany. College of Computing and Information.; Education, Higher--United States--Administration; Web Archives
Container List
- Web Archives, 2015 July 3-2016 September 28; nam_ua670-1; 596 captures
  Web crawling is managed through the Internet Archive's Archive-It service. This page includes links to both the university's collection and the Internet Archive's public collection.
  Surface-level crawling of www.albany.edu is performed daily which should includes most top-level webpages. Separate targeted crawls of every albany.edu subdomain are performed monthly to attempt to gather all content. This includes: www.albany.edu, www.rna.albany.edu, www.ctg.albany.edu, www.ualbanysports.com, www.albany.edu/rockefeller, www.albany.edu/cela, www.albany.edu/asrc, m.albany.edu, library.albany.edu, events.albany.edu, cstar.cestm.albany.edu, csda.albany.edu, and alumni.albany.edu
  Web Archives
  - http://www.albany.edu/ceas/ - University Archives collection, 2015 July 17-2016 September 28; nam_ua670-1_1 (Web-archive 1)
  - WARC file for http://www.albany.edu/ceas/, (please see https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Web_ARChive for more details), 2015 July 17-2016 September 28; nam_ua670-1_2 (Warc 1)
    WARC files are very large and difficult to work with. Your request may take time to process, and we may be unable to deliver your request remotely. Please consult an archivist if you are interested in researching with web archives.
  - http://www.albany.edu/ceas/ - Internet Archive collection, 2015 July 3-2016 September 28; nam_ua670-1_3 (Web-archive 2)
- Administrative Records, 2000-2015; nam_ua670-2; 15 cubic ft.
  - Academic Advisory Committee, Undated; nam_ua670-2_1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Restricted, contact archivist for more details.
  - ACT (program software), Undated; nam_ua670-2_2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Advisory Board, 2008 October; nam_ua670-2_3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Advisory Board Meeting (cancelled), 2014 April; nam_ua670-2_4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Advisory Board Meeting, 2012 April 19; nam_ua670-2_5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Advisory Board Meeting, 2009 November 17; nam_ua670-2_6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Albany, city of, Undated; nam_ua670-2_7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - ALA Accreditation 2010 (American Library Assoc.), Undated; nam_ua670-2_8 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - ALA Program 2010 (American Library Assoc.), Undated; nam_ua670-2_9 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - (ALA) American Library Association 2012, Undated; nam_ua670-2_10 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ALISE (Assoc. for Library & Info. Science Statistical, Undated; nam_ua670-2_11 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Alumni Association, Undated; nam_ua670-2_12 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Alumni (by Geographic Area), Undated; nam_ua670-2_13 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Alumni, 2004; nam_ua670-2_14 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Alumni Excellence Awards, 2012; nam_ua670-2_15 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Association Excellence Awards, 2012 April 28; nam_ua670-2_16 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Association Excellence Awards, 2013 April 20; nam_ua670-2_17 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Alumni Association Excellence Awards, 2013; nam_ua670-2_18 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Assoc. Excellence Awards, Deitsch, A., 2013-2014; nam_ua670-2_19 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Misc and Survey, Undated; nam_ua670-2_20 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Alumni Giving Letters, Undated; nam_ua670-2_21 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Untitled, 2012; nam_ua670-2_22 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Untitled, 2013; nam_ua670-2_23 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - ASIS&T Open Source Festival, 2012; nam_ua670-2_24 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Assessments, Undated; nam_ua670-2_25 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Assessments, Undated; nam_ua670-2_26 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Assessments, 2011; nam_ua670-2_27 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Assessments, 2013; nam_ua670-2_28 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Assessment Plans, Undated; nam_ua670-2_29 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - (College) Assessment Activity, Undated; nam_ua670-2_30 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Awards, Undated; nam_ua670-2_31 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Program Preservation M.S.I.S. Program, 2010; nam_ua670-2_32 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - 2004 Faculty Scholarly Program, nam_ua670-2_33 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - 2005 Faculty Scholarly Productivity Index, nam_ua670-2_34 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - BA in Information Science: Move from Infromation Studies to Informatics, Undated; nam_ua670-2_35 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - BAG-3, Undated; nam_ua670-2_36 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - BAG-3 Presentation, Undated; nam_ua670-2_37 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Bioinformatics, Undated; nam_ua670-2_38 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Bread and Roses Award - 7/18/13, 2013 July 18; nam_ua670-2_39 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Budget Hearing May 3, 2012, Undated; nam_ua670-2_40 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Budget, 2010-2011; nam_ua670-2_41 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Budget, 2009-2010; nam_ua670-2_42 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Budget, 2006-2007; nam_ua670-2_43 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Budget Meeting, 2006 April 3; nam_ua670-2_44 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Budget, 2005-2006; nam_ua670-2_45 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Budget-Grad Assistants, Undated; nam_ua670-2_46 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Budget Policies, Undated; nam_ua670-2_47 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Burton Lecture, 2006-2012; nam_ua670-2_48 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Campus Impact Statement, Undated; nam_ua670-2_49 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Capital Region Cyber Crime Partnership, Undated; nam_ua670-2_50 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Cyber Security Part 1, 2000-2010; nam_ua670-2_51 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Cyber Security Part 2, 2003-2008; nam_ua670-2_52 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Cyber Security Research Visit, 2008; nam_ua670-2_53 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Capital Region Economic Development Council, Undated; nam_ua670-2_54 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Career Panels, 2008-2009; nam_ua670-2_55 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Center for Technology in Government, 2002-2008; nam_ua670-2_56 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Center for Legislative Development, Undated; nam_ua670-2_57 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - CCI 2.0 Meetings, Undated; nam_ua670-2_58 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - CCI 2.0 Meetings, 2012; nam_ua670-2_59 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - CCI 2.0 Meetings, 2013; nam_ua670-2_60 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - CCI 2.0 Faculty Meetings, 2008; nam_ua670-2_61 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - CCI Faculty Meetings, Undated; nam_ua670-2_62 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - CCI Advisory Working Group, Undated; nam_ua670-2_63 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - CCI 2.0 Summer Planning Retreat, 2013; nam_ua670-2_64 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - CCI 2.0 Summer Planning Retreat, 2012; nam_ua670-2_65 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - CCI 2.0 Summer Planning, Undated; nam_ua670-2_66 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - CCI 2.0 Summer Planning Retreat, 2009; nam_ua670-2_67 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - CCI 2.0 Summer Planning Retreat, 2007; nam_ua670-2_68 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - CCI PR TU Article/letter, Undated; nam_ua670-2_69 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - CCI Chairs, Undated; nam_ua670-2_70 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - CCI Chairs Meeting, Undated; nam_ua670-2_71 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - CCI Chairs Retreat, Undated; nam_ua670-2_72 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - CCI Retreat, Undated; nam_ua670-2_73 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - CCI Executive Committee, Undated; nam_ua670-2_74 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - CCI Faculty, Undated; nam_ua670-2_75 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - CCI Hiring Plans, Undated; nam_ua670-2_76 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - CCI Hiring Plans 05/06, Undated; nam_ua670-2_77 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - CCI History, Undated; nam_ua670-2_78 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - CCI MOU, Undated; nam_ua670-2_79 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - CCI Space Needs, 2009; nam_ua670-2_80 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - CCI Times (SISP), Undated; nam_ua670-2_81 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - CCI Welcome Back Gathering, 2009-2011; 2013; nam_ua670-2_82 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - CCI WIT, Undated; nam_ua670-2_83 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Community Engagement, Undated; nam_ua670-2_84 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Community Engagement, Presidents Awards, 2014; nam_ua670-2_85 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Community Engagement Red Dot Series, Undated; nam_ua670-2_86 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - CCUCE / Campus Comm. on Uni Community Engagement, Undated; nam_ua670-2_87 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - CCUCE / Dr. Andrew Furco, Undated; nam_ua670-2_88 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - CDLC, Undated; nam_ua670-2_89 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - CEG, Undated; nam_ua670-2_90 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - CEG/NIJ PROPOSAL, Undated; nam_ua670-2_91 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - CFMR Proposal, Undated; nam_ua670-2_92 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - CI Brochures, Undated; nam_ua670-2_93 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - CIFA, Undated; nam_ua670-2_94 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - CIFA/CSCIC Meeting, Undated; nam_ua670-2_95 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - CIFA Grand Opening, Undated; nam_ua670-2_96 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - CIFA PR, Undated; nam_ua670-2_97 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - CIFA Presentations, Undated; nam_ua670-2_98 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - CIFA Resources, Undated; nam_ua670-2_99 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Clippings, Undated; nam_ua670-2_100 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - CNVRC, Undated; nam_ua670-2_101 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Commencement Part 1, 2014; nam_ua670-2_102 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Commencement Part 2, 2014; nam_ua670-2_103 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Commencement, 2014 December; nam_ua670-2_104 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Commencement, 2013; nam_ua670-2_105 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Commencement Program, 2013; nam_ua670-2_106 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Commencement, 2012; nam_ua670-2_107 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Commencement, 2011; nam_ua670-2_108 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Commencement, 2010; nam_ua670-2_109 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Commencement, 2009; nam_ua670-2_110 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Commencement, 2007-2008; nam_ua670-2_111 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Commencement, 2005-2006; nam_ua670-2_112 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - CCI Valedictorian, Undated; nam_ua670-2_113 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Compact Planning, Undated; nam_ua670-2_114 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Compact Plan, Undated; nam_ua670-2_115 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Compact Plan CCI Raw Notes, Undated; nam_ua670-2_116 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Compact Plan CCI, Undated; nam_ua670-2_117 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Compact Plan, Undated; nam_ua670-2_118 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Compact Plan DFA Informatics, Undated; nam_ua670-2_119 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Compact Plan, Undated; nam_ua670-2_120 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Compact Plan, Undated; nam_ua670-2_121 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Compact Plan Other Units, Undated; nam_ua670-2_122 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Companies-MISC, Undated; nam_ua670-2_123 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Computer Science Cor, Undated; nam_ua670-2_124 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Computer Science, 2012; nam_ua670-2_125 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Computer Science, 2011; nam_ua670-2_126 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Computer Science, 2010; nam_ua670-2_127 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Computer Science, 2009; nam_ua670-2_128 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Computer Science Course Action Forms, Undated; nam_ua670-2_129 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Computer Science Scholarship recipient, 2014 Fall; nam_ua670-2_130 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Computer Science Scholarship recipient, 2013 Fall; nam_ua670-2_131 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Computer Science Scholarships, 2014-2015; nam_ua670-2_132 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Computer Science Scholarship recipient, 2015 Spring; nam_ua670-2_133 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Computer Science Scholarship recipient, 2014 Spring; nam_ua670-2_134 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Conference CISSE, 2003 June; nam_ua670-2_135 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Conference ECPI Georgia, 2004 March; nam_ua670-2_136 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Conference Penn State, Undated; nam_ua670-2_137 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Undated; nam_ua670-2_138 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence Hall, Kermit, Undated; nam_ua670-2_139 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence Herbst, Susan, Undated; nam_ua670-2_140 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence Philip, George, Undated; nam_ua670-2_141 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence Phillips, Susan, Undated; nam_ua670-2_142 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence Spencer, Melinda, Undated; nam_ua670-2_143 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Council on Competitiveness, Undated; nam_ua670-2_144 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Course Action Forms 2014, nam_ua670-2_145 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Course Action Forms, 2012-2013; nam_ua670-2_146 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Course Planning - University, Undated; nam_ua670-2_147 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - CPATH, 2011; nam_ua670-2_148 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - CPATH, Undated; nam_ua670-2_149 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - CPATH (Executive), Undated; nam_ua670-2_150 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - CPATH Proposals, Undated; nam_ua670-2_151 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - CE 21, Undated; nam_ua670-2_152 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - CRA Deans, Undated; nam_ua670-2_153 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Creation of College, Undated; nam_ua670-2_154 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - CRISNY, Undated; nam_ua670-2_155 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - CSC, Undated; nam_ua670-2_156 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - NSF CPATH, Undated; nam_ua670-2_157 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Grants CPATH, Undated; nam_ua670-2_158 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Grant Proposal-NSF CPATH, 2009; nam_ua670-2_159 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Grant Proposal-NSF CPATH, Undated; nam_ua670-2_160 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Gurin, Joel Visit-CTG, Undated; nam_ua670-2_161 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - PFMR, Undated; nam_ua670-2_162 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - PFMR-PR, Undated; nam_ua670-2_163 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - PFMR-Proposals, Undated; nam_ua670-2_164 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - PFMR- Reports and Commentaries, 2009; nam_ua670-2_165 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - PFMR-Resources, Undated; nam_ua670-2_166 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Course Redesign, Undated; nam_ua670-2_167 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - CRA (Computing Research Association), Undated; nam_ua670-2_168 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - CRA Deans, Undated; nam_ua670-2_169 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - CRA Snowbird Conference, 2014; nam_ua670-2_170 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - CRA Snowbird, 2010; nam_ua670-2_171 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - CRA Snowbird, 2006; nam_ua670-2_172 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Lists of Names, Undated; nam_ua670-2_173 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - CSCIC, Undated; nam_ua670-2_174 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - CSCIC Education Sector, Undated; nam_ua670-2_175 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - CSCIC Cyber Academy, Undated; nam_ua670-2_176 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Cyber Security Webcasts, Undated; nam_ua670-2_177 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - CTG, Undated; nam_ua670-2_178 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Grant Proposal - Misc, Undated; nam_ua670-2_179 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Grant Proposal - NSF, 1999; nam_ua670-2_180 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Grant Proposal - RIT/NSF, Undated; nam_ua670-2_181 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - CTG Brochures, Undated; nam_ua670-2_182 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - CWIG, Undated; nam_ua670-2_183 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Dashboard, Undated; nam_ua670-2_184 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Deans Council History, Undated; nam_ua670-2_185 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Deans Council, 2008; nam_ua670-2_186 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Deans Office Meetings, Undated; nam_ua670-2_187 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Development Companies, Undated; nam_ua670-2_188 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Development- CA, Undated; nam_ua670-2_189 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Development- Prospects, Undated; nam_ua670-2_190 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - DG.O, Undated; nam_ua670-2_191 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Digging into Data, Undated; nam_ua670-2_192 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Digigirlz, 2010; 2013; nam_ua670-2_193 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Digigirlz Event, Undated; nam_ua670-2_194 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Doctoral Review, Undated; nam_ua670-2_195 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Downtown Deans, Undated; nam_ua670-2_196 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Empire Innovative Program, Undated; nam_ua670-2_197 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Enrollment, Undated; nam_ua670-2_198 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Enrollment Planning, Undated; nam_ua670-2_199 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Equitable Contributions, Undated; nam_ua670-2_200 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Ethiopia Project, Undated; nam_ua670-2_201 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Expeditions, Undated; nam_ua670-2_202 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Faculty Activity Reports, Undated; nam_ua670-2_203 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - File Mangement, Undated; nam_ua670-2_204 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - FINRA, Undated; nam_ua670-2_205 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - FIPSE, 2002; nam_ua670-2_206 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - FIPSE, 2006; nam_ua670-2_207 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - FIPSE Meetings, Undated; nam_ua670-2_208 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Financial Analysis Stream, 2004-2006; nam_ua670-2_209 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - FMR Advisory, Undated; nam_ua670-2_210 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - FMR, Undated; nam_ua670-2_211 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - FMR-Props, Undated; nam_ua670-2_212 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Food For Thought, Undated; nam_ua670-2_213 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Forensics, Undated; nam_ua670-2_214 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - FRAP, Undated; nam_ua670-2_215 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Gates Foundation Grant, Undated; nam_ua670-2_216 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Gainful Employment Reporting, Undated; nam_ua670-2_217 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - General Education Task Force, Undated; nam_ua670-2_218 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Global Game Jam, Undated; nam_ua670-2_219 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Government Relations, Undated; nam_ua670-2_220 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Government Website - Commercial, Undated; nam_ua670-2_221 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Grace Hopper, 2007-2011; nam_ua670-2_222 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Grade Change Forms, Undated; nam_ua670-2_223 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Graduate Assistantships, Fellowships and Tuition, Undated; nam_ua670-2_224 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Government Website, Undated; nam_ua670-2_225 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Graduate Enrollment Target, Undated; nam_ua670-2_226 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Grad Fair, Undated; nam_ua670-2_227 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Grad Studies, Undated; nam_ua670-2_228 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Graystone, Undated; nam_ua670-2_229 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - GSS Review, Undated; nam_ua670-2_230 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - GSS, 2011-2012; nam_ua670-2_231 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Grant Tech Connex, Undated; nam_ua670-2_232 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Harriman, Undated; nam_ua670-2_233 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Harriman Campus, Undated; nam_ua670-2_234 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Harriman Campus Space, Undated; nam_ua670-2_235 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Harriman - External, Undated; nam_ua670-2_236 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Harriman Incubator, Undated; nam_ua670-2_237 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Harriman - Internal UAlbany, Undated; nam_ua670-2_238 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Harriman Proposals, Undated; nam_ua670-2_239 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Harriman Reseach and Technology Park Part 1, 2006; nam_ua670-2_240 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Harriman Reseach and Technology Park Part 2, 2006; nam_ua670-2_241 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Health Informatics, Undated; nam_ua670-2_242 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - HEGIS Codes, Undated; nam_ua670-2_243 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Historical Documents (Important), Undated; nam_ua670-2_244 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Hitchcock, Karen (Park Strategies), Undated; nam_ua670-2_245 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Holiday Cards, Undated; nam_ua670-2_246 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Holiday Cards, Undated; nam_ua670-2_247 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Holiday Cards, Undated; nam_ua670-2_248 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Homeland Security (ARPA), Undated; nam_ua670-2_249 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Homeland Security UAlbany, Undated; nam_ua670-2_250 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Honors College, Undated; nam_ua670-2_251 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Honors Society, Undated; nam_ua670-2_252 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Husted Hall Renovations, Undated; nam_ua670-2_253 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - IBM, Undated; nam_ua670-2_254 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - IBM, Undated; nam_ua670-2_255 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - IBM Collaborative Technologies, 2006-2008; nam_ua670-2_256 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - IBM Pangoon, Undated; nam_ua670-2_257 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - IBM Proposal, Undated; nam_ua670-2_258 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - IBM Research, 2007-2008; nam_ua670-2_259 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - IBM Resources, Undated; nam_ua670-2_260 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - FMR Executive Board, Undated; nam_ua670-2_261 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - FMT, 2008; nam_ua670-2_262 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Ice Gov Brochure, Undated; nam_ua670-2_263 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - IFMR Conference, Undated; nam_ua670-2_264 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - IFMR Working Group, Undated; nam_ua670-2_265 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - IFW, Undated; nam_ua670-2_266 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - IMLS, Undated; nam_ua670-2_267 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - IMLS Diversity Proposal, 2009; nam_ua670-2_268 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - INF Proposal, Undated; nam_ua670-2_269 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Informatics, 2005; nam_ua670-2_270 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Informatics, 2006-2009; nam_ua670-2_271 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Informatics - B.S. Degree, 2014; nam_ua670-2_272 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Informatics Course Action Forms, Undated; nam_ua670-2_273 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Informatics, Doctoral Program Review, Undated; nam_ua670-2_274 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Informatics Meeting, Undated; nam_ua670-2_275 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Informatics Ph.D., Undated; nam_ua670-2_276 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Informatics Ph.D. Admissions, Undated; nam_ua670-2_277 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Informatics (INF)-Ph.D., Undated; nam_ua670-2_278 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Informatics Ph.D. Student, Undated; nam_ua670-2_279 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Informatics The New School Org Chart, Undated; nam_ua670-2_280 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Information Science BA, Undated; nam_ua670-2_281 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Informatics (INF)-Space, Undated; nam_ua670-2_282 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Informatics Task force, Undated; nam_ua670-2_283 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Informatics Redesign, Undated; nam_ua670-2_284 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - INF Retreat, Undated; nam_ua670-2_285 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - INF Scheduling Requests, Undated; nam_ua670-2_286 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Information Science General, Undated; nam_ua670-2_287 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Information Science PACIST Report, Undated; nam_ua670-2_288 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Information Science Planning Documents, Undated; nam_ua670-2_289 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Information Science Provosts Advisory Committee, Undated; nam_ua670-2_290 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Information Security, Undated; nam_ua670-2_291 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Information Studies, Undated; nam_ua670-2_292 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Information Studies, Undated; nam_ua670-2_293 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Information Studies, Undated; nam_ua670-2_294 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Information Studies (Course Action Forms), Undated; nam_ua670-2_295 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Info Studies Retreat, Undated; nam_ua670-2_296 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Info Studies, 2012; nam_ua670-2_297 (Box 8, Folder 4)